<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coDesign</title>
    <link>https://thecodesign.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on coDesign</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thecodesign.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The reason you&#39;re here</title>
      <link>https://thecodesign.io/blog/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thecodesign.io/blog/introduction/</guid>
      <description>I am a code+design enthusiast; and I’m sure since you’re reading this, you’re one as well. I’m an avid reader as well, and for obvious reasons, I’m going to go ahead and assume you’re one too.
I’ve been reading articles on the internet for a decade now, and I know the annoyance one feels when the article they’re presented with, is just a place-holder with more than 70% of padding. The noise- is too much; is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us, our product and our community.</title>
      <link>https://thecodesign.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thecodesign.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us, our product and our community.  Separating the signal from the noise, we curate only the most qualitative and the most relavant code+design content. A fresh, noise-free podcast every Wednesday and a Newsletter every Sunday.
 Take me to the curation Tell me more       &#34;coDesign&#34; has the features you want.   Ditch all the noise Focus on the content that matters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache License (Legal)</title>
      <link>https://thecodesign.io/legal/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thecodesign.io/legal/license/</guid>
      <description>Switch to:
  Terms of Service Privacy Policy Open Source Software License Copy   &amp;nbsp;
Terms and Conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution 1. Definitions “License” shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.
“Licensor” shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.
“Legal Entity” shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy (Legal)</title>
      <link>https://thecodesign.io/legal/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thecodesign.io/legal/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Switch to:
  Terms of Service Privacy Policy Open Source Software License Copy   0. Welcome to coDesign! We care about your privacy and want to help you understand how we collect, use and share your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of coDesign, and is part of our Terms of Service.
Reading this Privacy Policy should be pretty easy as we’ve made sure to avoid any legal jargon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service (Legal)</title>
      <link>https://thecodesign.io/legal/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thecodesign.io/legal/terms/</guid>
      <description>Switch to:
  Terms of Service Privacy Policy Open Source Software License Copy   0. Welcome to coDesign! Hi there! This is the coDesign Terms of Service (stick with us). Most of the time, these documents are not quite easy to get through, but we have done everything we can to make reading this document simpler and maybe even a bit fun. Maybe. These summaries are not legally binding, but they give you a short version of the agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome! (Legal)</title>
      <link>https://thecodesign.io/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thecodesign.io/legal/</guid>
      <description>Switch to:
  Terms of Service Privacy Policy Open Source Software License Copy   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>